That one star in the night sky
밤하늘 속에 저 별 하나
Seems to be shining brighter
유독 돋보이게 빛나
You and I sitting side by side
너와 나 둘이 나란히 앉아
The day we spent a quiet night
조용한 밤 보낸 날
You had your head up only watching
너는 고개를 계속 든 채 하늘만
the sky but
바라보고 있었겠지만
For me your side-profile shines brighter
나는 너의 그 옆모습이 별보다
than the stars, my baby
빛나 보여 My baby
The deepening night
짙어진 밤
The night the moon and stars
저 달도 별들도 너에게 질투한 그 밤
were jealous of you
Let the both of us remember that day
서로 그날을 기억해
Last night, the words you and I spoke
Last night 너와 내가 했던 말
Moonlight, my reflection in your eyes
Moonlight 너의 눈에 비친 나
Ma ma ma ma ma ma my love
The love we promised
약속했던 사랑
Beautiful Last night
I’ll hold you like the night breeze
밤바람처럼 안아줄게
I hope you never leave my arms
내 품에서 안 떠났으면 해
So that you can remember today
오늘을 평생 기억할 수 있게
for a lifetime
I’ll even pick the stars for you
저 별이라도 따줄게
Yeah, our night full of excitement
Yeah 우리의 설렜던 밤
The night we promised our future
미래를 기약하던 밤
You, who holds the stars of the universe
우주의 별을 담은 너의
I’ll become your moon
달이 되어 줄게
The love I gave you
네가 달라 하기도 전에 네게 준 사랑
even before you asked for it
I pray that you’ll accept it
받아주길 바라 기도로 꾹 담아
I’m the Romeo who serves you tonight
난 오늘 밤 널 모시는 Romeo
I’ve probably always been yours
아마 원래부터 난 네 것이었어
The deepening night
짙어진 밤
The night the moon and stars
저 달도 별들도 너에게 질투한 그 밤
were jealous of you
Let the both of us remember that day
서로 그날을 기억해
Last night, the words you and I spoke
Last night 너와 내가 했던 말
Moonlight, my reflection in your eyes
Moonlight 너의 눈에 비친 나
Ma ma ma ma ma ma my love
The love we promised
약속했던 사랑
Beautiful Last night
Ooh ooh ooh
You and me, Last night
너와 내 Last night
Ooh ooh ooh
Beautiful Last night
Last night
I’ll remember that day forever
영원히 기억해 그날
Moonlight
The day I danced with you
아래 너와 춤추던 날
Last night
I’ll remember that day forever
영원히 기억해 그날
Moonlight
The day I danced with you
아래 너와 춤추던 날
Last night, the words you spoke to me
Last night 네가 내게 건네준 말
Moonlight, even your reflection in it
Moonlight 비춰진 네 모습도 다
Ma ma ma ma ma ma my love
The love we promised
약속했던 사랑
You and me, Last night
너와 내 Last night